Animal Crossing is a game where you take out a housing loan
And instead of getting a stable job
you throw a live fish in a wooden box
There has got to be an easier way to pay this off!
Today I am gonna show you how to become filthy rich
and beat the game
"Killian, you can't beat the game"
"Animal Crossing has no ending"
Really?
Because New Leaf could be beaten in 208 hours
And knowing my videogame skills
I can probably do it in 207
Animal Crossing is supposed to be a relaxing game
That makes you weak, vulnerable to attack
I recommend not showing up for work
The e-mails threatening you that you will lose it, will keep you alive
Let's Start
We are welcomed by Timmy and Tommy
sons of the richest person in videogame history
Thomas Grand Nook 1st
We are moving to a deserted Island
located in, based on local fish and insects
Earth... All of it... At the same time
Pick your name, don't include personal info
I am so serious about beating this game
I'm gonna break the first command given to me
I wonder what this looks like
Where do you live now? Is Nintendo doxxing me?
Considering current events, maybe I shouldn't pick Europe
Do I really have to choose this planet?
Ahh... out of solidarity
We are off to our deserted island, taught zero survival skills
Two days until Lord of the Flies
Fortunately you get two animal friends to start with, to help you out
Mine are Antonio, ant eater
no ants on the island... So he's usless
and a pig. Before you ask, No you are not allowed to hunt your island friends
We finally meet the main man himself
dressed like a mafia boss, not even trying to hide it anymore
Set down your tent and other tents
To celebrate our move Tom is making some barbecue cherries...
I've made a huge mistake, please take me back to civilization!
I can't live a fruttarian lifestyle
What to name the island?
The location I am on, is an island
so what about.. The Island
That was a prologue
Go to bed and a celebrity dog invades your brain and explains general relativity and space time...
When you wake up, Tom gives you a smartphone
Yes, he produces smarthphones too
Fortunately, children didn't assemble it
because they would be like cubs, or like piglets
My first goal shall be to get a house
By paying off the first loan of 5000 Nook miles
Achievement points
Get them by cleaning the island
catching fish, bugs... This is kind of relaxing... and fun
I... I have an idea
What if I enjoyed my time
and played a videogame for entertainment purposes?
Heresy, I know, but...
I'm... I'm gonna try it
Getting to 5000 miles was easy!
I only had to catch 2610 fishes
Now I have a house!
Guys really live in apartments like this and don't see the issue
Next an owl moves in and he wants me to give him fossiles
Sure! Good thing we don't have preservation laws
And good thing every dinosaur, in every period lived on this island
This used to be Dino-Manhattan
After collecting 20 different things
He can submit an application to create our museum
Submit an application to whom?
Who are these mysterious benefactors?
There's something bigger going on here!
But i have debts, so I will not question the status-quo
After a 30 million bells museum was built overnight
We could really use a shop to boost our economy
To build a shop we need wood and iron
Can get wood by chopping
but it's cheaper to ask Tom to import some
from the "Nook Amazon Logging Company"™
Iron you get from punching rocks
I would test out this theory outside, but I'm scared to leave my house
I destroyed all the rocks on my island
because... I'm a moron
but don't worry! Spend achievement points to travel to random islands
Here you can also find new residents for your island
Why invite them? They don't pay any rent
Uhm... You want to complain if your island gets invaded
and you wanna go full crits on the invaders
Now we have a store, Nice!
Time to go back to providing free labour for a tanuki
Oh.. Ok, he pays in a fence
This was worth it
If anyone steps in my yard, I'm getting the slingshot
After fishing some more, I finally paid off my first money loan
Now I have a bigger house
The LED lights under the lava did not cost extra
Now I only have to bring that doggy pop star to the island
And I will have unlocked everything
Should go pretty fast
Nope! There was an Easter event
Slow down the game by 400%
But by selling all the eggs I got, I could afford another loan
Now I have a new room to store Easter stuff
Jesus, your death sure led to unexpected consequences
Eventually, after planting 50 flowers
the dog decided to show up
I beat the game!
No! I have unpaid loans
So now the focus should be to make as much money as possible
How?
Spiders and turnips
In real life a tarantula costs 50 dollars
In animal crossing they sell for 1/10 of an house
You can create an island that spawns only spiders
They will chase and kill you
And the stress of this will kill ou in real life
But it's worth it
I managed to save up 500,000
Now I will spend all of that on turnips
which are something you invest in
Turnips are a Japanese pun for stocks
doesn't translate, so it should be removed from the game
But for now I will do like I did with Doge Coin
and bet Everything
Ready to make my fortune
My first day as a future Master of the Animals
It's called a Black Saturday
When you are forced to sell your turnips for 40 bells
After taxes and bribes to get through turnip sanctions
I actually owed money
I had nothing...
And it was all my fault
I played Animal Crossing like a relaxing game
Such a weak mindset!
I stopped getting angry and I lost twice
How will I ever get my money back Tom?
Do I know what a "fugazi" is?